[
    [
        "Dell 14 Laptop, 13th Gen Intel Core i5-1335U Processor/ 8GB/ 512GB SSD/ 14.0\" (35.56cm) FHD/Windows 11 + MSO'21/15 Month McAfee/Spill-Resistant Keyboard/Carbon Black/Thin & Light- 1.46kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    5,
                    7,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    25,
                    30,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    61,
                    64,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    66,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    76,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    99,
                    "MONEY"
                ],
                [
                    121,
                    172,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    186,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Swift 3 (2024) - Intel Core i7-1250U, 54WHrs Battery - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics) Ultrabook (14 Inch, Pure Silver, 1.20 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    18,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    49,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    73,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    99,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    105,
                    117,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    136,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    151,
                    155,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Samsung Galaxy Book3 Ultra 2 (2024) - Dynamic AMOLED 2X Display, Intel EVO Platform, 76WHrs Battery, Intel Core i9-13900HX - (32 GB/2 TB SSD/Windows 11 Pro/RTX 4080/100 W) NP960XFH-X02US Laptop (16 Inch, Graphite, 1.85 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    91,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    126,
                    133,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    134,
                    151,
                    "FAC"
                ],
                [
                    195,
                    202,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    214,
                    218,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS Vivobook 16X, Intel Core i7-12650H 12th Gen, 16-inch (40.64 cm) FHD+, Creator/Gaming Laptop, (16 GB RAM/512GB SSD/8GB RTX 4050/Win11/Backlit/FP/70WHr /Black/3.97 kg), K3605ZV-MBN741WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    13,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    17,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    19,
                    29,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    44,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    45,
                    48,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    57,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    67,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    99,
                    101,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    104,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    114,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    120,
                    "NORP"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    122,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    131,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    145,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo ThinkPad X1 Carbon Gen 11 (2024) - 12th Gen Intel Core i7-1260P, 57WHrs Battery - (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Pro/Intel Iris Xe Graphics) Ultrabook (14 Inch, Black, 1.12 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    16,
                    32,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    38,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    61,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    78,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    90,
                    92,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    125,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    143,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    155,
                    169,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    171,
                    175,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo LOQ AI Powered AMD Ryzen 7 7840HS 15.6\" (39.6cm) FHD IPS 144Hz 350Nits Gaming Laptop (16GB/512GB SSD/Win 11/NVIDIA RTX 3050 6GB/Office 2021/3 Month Game Pass/Storm Grey/2.4Kg), 82XT004HIN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    33,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    45,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    54,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    91,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    101,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    103,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    141,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    142,
                    154,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    184,
                    194,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Samsung Galaxy Book3 Core i7 13th Gen 1355U - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home) Galaxy Book3 Thin and Light Laptop (15.6 Inch, Graphite, 1.58 Kg, with MS Office)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    43,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    59,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    79,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    115,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    117,
                    126,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    142,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    145,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    152,
                    161,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Apple MacBook Air 15 (2024) - Apple M3, 52.6WHrs Battery - (8 GB/512 GB SSD/macOS/Integrated Graphics) Ultrabook (15.6 Inch, Midnight, 1.30 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    38,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    48,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    71,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    112,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    114,
                    123,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    135,
                    139,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Aspire 5 (2024) - Intel Core i5-1235U, 48WHrs Battery - (8 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics) Laptop (15.6 Inch, Silver, 1.80 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    13,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    19,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    37,
                    42,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    44,
                    50,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    99,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    105,
                    117,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    126,
                    135,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    143,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    145,
                    149,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Apple MacBook Pro 16 (2024) - Apple M3 Max, 100WHrs Battery - (32 GB/1 TB SSD/macOS/Integrated Graphics) Ultrabook (16 Inch, Space Grey, 2.00 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    35,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    42,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    44,
                    51,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    65,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    144,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo E41-55 Laptop Ryzen 3-3250U|8Gb Ram|1Tb 7200Rpm HDD/Dos|2Cell 30Wh/WiFi Bt/Cam/No Fpr/|14\" Hd Inches|1 Year Onsite Warranty/Iron Grey|82Fj00A0Ih,AMD",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    27,
                    38,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    54,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    73,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    152,
                    155,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS ROG Zephyrus G14 (2022), 14\" (35.56 cm) FHD+ 16:10 144Hz/3ms, AMD Ryzen 7 6800HS, 8GB Radeon RX 6700S, Gaming Laptop (16GB/1TB SSD/Windows 11/with Office/Eclipse Gray/1.65 Kg), GA402RJZ-L4134WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    23,
                    27,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    32,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    35,
                    43,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    65,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    76,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    77,
                    85,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    90,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    121,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    146,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    182,
                    198,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Infinix INBook Y1 (2024) - HD Display, Intel Pentium Silver N6000, 42WHrs Battery - (4 GB/128 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/UHD Graphics/45 W) Y1-14 Laptop (14 Inch, Black, 1.48 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    19,
                    23,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    53,
                    65,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    73,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    86,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    96,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    97,
                    134,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    136,
                    138,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    150,
                    164,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    166,
                    173,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS ROG Strix G17 (2022) Gaming Laptop,AMD Ryzen 7-6800HS,17.3-inch (43.94 cms) FHD 144Hz, RTX 3050 4GB Graphics,(16GB RAM/512GB SSD/Windows 11/Gray/2.5 Kg),G713RC-HX109WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    20,
                    24,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    49,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    68,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    79,
                    "MONEY"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    90,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    92,
                    95,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    102,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    104,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    117,
                    119,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    129,
                    "GPE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell G16-7630 Gaming 13th Gen Laptop, Intel i7-13650HX/32GB/1TB SSD/NVIDIA RTX 4060, 8GB GDDR6/16 inch (40.64cm) QHD+ 165Hz 3ms sRGB-100%/Win 11 + MSO'21/McAfee 15 Month/Metallic Nightshade/2.87kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    25,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    26,
                    36,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    43,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    83,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    88,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    111,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    142,
                    146,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    147,
                    160,
                    "EVENT"
                ],
                [
                    161,
                    178,
                    "DATE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HP Pavilion 15 (2024) - AMD Ryzen 7 5700U, 41WHrs Battery - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/AMD Radeon Graphics) Laptop (15.6 Inch, Natural Silver, 1.75 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    34,
                    41,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    49,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    73,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    121,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    132,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    150,
                    154,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HP Pavilion 14, 12th Gen Intel Core i5-1235U, 14-inch (35.6 cm), FHD, 16GB DDR4, 512GB SSD, Intel Iris Xe graphics, FPR, 720p HD camera, Backlit KB (Win 11, MSO 2021, Silver, 1.41 kg), dv2014TU",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    30,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    44,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    53,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    62,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    72,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    74,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    81,
                    84,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    86,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    92,
                    97,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    105,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    119,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    121,
                    125,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    137,
                    147,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    155,
                    "LAW"
                ],
                [
                    161,
                    165,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    167,
                    173,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    175,
                    182,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Swift Go 14 Thin and Light Premium Laptop AMD Ryzen 5 7530U Hexa-Core Processor (8GB/ 512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/MS Office Home and Student) Pure Silver, SFG14-41, 35.56 cm (14.0\") Full HD",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    14,
                    16,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    56,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    58,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    64,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    84,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    94,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    95,
                    97,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    144,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    169,
                    177,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    179,
                    183,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell Inspiron 13 7000 (2024) - 12th Gen Intel Core i7-12700H, 56WHrs Battery - (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics) Ultrabook (13.3 Inch, Silver, 1.35 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    21,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    23,
                    27,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    36,
                    50,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    60,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    62,
                    68,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    82,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    116,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    122,
                    134,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    146,
                    155,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    165,
                    172,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS Zenbook S 13 OLED (2023), 1kg Weight & 1cm Thin, Intel Core EVO i5 13th Gen, 13.3 Inch 2.8K OLED, Thin & Light Laptop (16GB/512GB SSD/Iris Xe/Win 11/Office 2021/63WHrs/Blue), UX5304VA-NQ541WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    28,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    31,
                    34,
                    "MONEY"
                ],
                [
                    35,
                    47,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    54,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    91,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    122,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    124,
                    132,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    132,
                    134,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    139,
                    150,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Chromebook Intel Celeron Dual-Core N4500 (Chrome OS/8 GB/128 GB eMMC) CB314-3H with 35.5 cm (14\") HD Display, Pure Silver, 1.45 KG",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    39,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    53,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    66,
                    68,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    96,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    126,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    135,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS Vivobook 15, Intel Celeron N4020, 15.6\" (39.62 cms) HD, Thin and Light Laptop (8GB/512GB SSD/Integrated Graphics/Windows 11/Office 2021/Silver/1.8 kg), X515MA-BR022WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    18,
                    37,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    43,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    46,
                    51,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    61,
                    82,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    93,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    135,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    136,
                    140,
                    "DATE"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Predator Helios Neo 16 Gaming Laptop 13th Gen Intel Core i7 Processor (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/NVIDIA Â® GeForce RTX Â¢ 4050) PHN16-71, (16\") WUXGA Display",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    27,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    78,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    124,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    136,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    151,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Swift X Sfx14-41G Creator Laptop Thin & Light 14 Inches Full Hd 100% Srgb AMD Ryzen 7 5800U Nvidia RTX 3050Ti Laptop Graphics 16Gb Lpddr4X 1Tb Ssd Backlit Kb 1.39Kg Mso Windows 11 Home",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    21,
                    68,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    73,
                    "PERCENT"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    96,
                    "PERCENT"
                ],
                [
                    108,
                    114,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    130,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    148,
                    159,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    163,
                    169,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    170,
                    189,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HP Victus Gaming Laptop, AMD Ryzen 5 5600H, 4GB AMD Radeon RX 6500M graphics, 15.6-inch (39.6 cm), FHD,MSO,144Hz, 8GB DDR4, 512GB SSD, Backlit KB, B&O, Dual speakers (Silver, 2.37 kg), fb0158AX",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    34,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    35,
                    42,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    44,
                    45,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    45,
                    47,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    48,
                    67,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    87,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    96,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    99,
                    102,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    103,
                    112,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    115,
                    117,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    124,
                    127,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    129,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    135,
                    145,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    147,
                    150,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    175,
                    182,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell G15-5530 Gaming Laptop, Intel Core i5-13450HX Processor, 16GB DDR5, 1TB, NVIDIA RTX 3050,6GB GDDR6, 15.6\" (39.62cm) FHD 120Hz 250 nits, Backlit KB Orange,Win 11 + MSO'21, Dark Shadow Gray, 2.65kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    5,
                    13,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    27,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    39,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    50,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    62,
                    64,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    66,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    74,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    76,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    84,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    95,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    95,
                    103,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    105,
                    109,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    120,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    125,
                    134,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    158,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    194,
                    200,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "LG Gram Convertible 14 (2024) - WQXGA IPS Touch Display, Intel EVO Platform, 72WHrs Battery, Intel Core i7-13750U - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/65 W) 14T90R-K.AAS7U1 Convertible Laptop (14 Inch, Dark Silver, 1.05 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    20,
                    28,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    77,
                    83,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    93,
                    103,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    127,
                    129,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    130,
                    149,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    150,
                    171,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    173,
                    179,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    209,
                    216,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    231,
                    235,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "LG Gram 13 (2024) - WUXGA IPS Display, Intel EVO Platform, 72WHrs Battery, Intel Core i5-13500U - (8 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/65 W) 13Z90R-K.AAS6U1 Laptop (13 Inch, Obsidian Black, 0.98 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    16,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    65,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    85,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    111,
                    130,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    152,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    154,
                    160,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    178,
                    185,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    203,
                    210,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell XPS 9730 Laptop, Intel Core i7-13700H Processor/32GB DDR5/1TB SSD/NVIDIA RTX 4060 8GB GDDR6/17.0\" (43.18cm) UHD+ AR Touch 500 nits/Backlit KB + FPR/Win 11 + MSO'21 + 15 Month McAfee/Silver/2.44kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    22,
                    32,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    64,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    82,
                    88,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    90,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    101,
                    "NORP"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    111,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    136,
                    148,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    180,
                    186,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Infinix INBook Y1 Pro (2024) - HD Display, Intel Pentium Silver N6000, 42WHrs Battery - (4 GB/256 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/UHD Graphics/45 W) Y1-14 Pro Laptop (14 Inch, Black, 1.49 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    23,
                    27,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    69,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    77,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    90,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    142,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    158,
                    172,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    181,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Predator Helios Neo 16 Gaming Laptop 13th Gen Intel Core i7 Processor (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/NVIDIA Â® GeForce RTX Â¢ 4050) PHN16-71, (16\") WUXGA Display",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    25,
                    27,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    78,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    124,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    129,
                    136,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    151,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "MSI Gaming GL63 9SD-1042IN Intel Core i5-9300H 9th Gen 15.6-inch Gaming Laptop(8GB/1TB HDD + 256GB NVMe SSD/Windows 10 Home/GTX 1660 Ti, 6GB Graphics/Black/2.22Kg) 9S7-16P732-1043",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    16,
                    26,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    27,
                    32,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    64,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    98,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    132,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    149,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    164,
                    167,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo V15 G3 (82TTA01EIN) Laptop (Intel Core i3-1215U/ 8GB RAM/ 512GB SSD/DOS/ 15.6\" FHD/ 1 Year Warranty), Iron Grey",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    6,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    7,
                    13,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    35,
                    40,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    57,
                    59,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    65,
                    68,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    68,
                    70,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    84,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    106,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    118,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS Zenbook 14 Flip OLED (2023), Intel Core EVO i5-1340P 13th Gen, 14\" (35.56 cm) 2.8K 90Hz OLED, Thin & Light Laptop (16GB/512GB SSD/Windows 11/Office 2021/75WHr/Silver/1.5 kg) UP3404VA-KN543WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    12,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    27,
                    31,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    48,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    49,
                    62,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    68,
                    70,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    81,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    86,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    99,
                    118,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    128,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    130,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    152,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "LG Gram 2-in-1 16 (2024) - WQXGA IPS Touch Display, Intel EVO Platform, 80WHrs Battery, Intel Core i7-13750H - (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/90 W) 16T90R-K.AAS8U1 Convertible Laptop (16 Inch, Dark Silver, 1.48 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    72,
                    78,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    98,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    112,
                    114,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    142,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    164,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    166,
                    172,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    202,
                    209,
                    "TIME"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "MSI Prestige 16 Studio, Intel 13th Gen. i7-13700H, 41CM QHD+ 165Hz Laptop (16GB/1TB NVMe SSD/Windows 11 Home/Nvidia GeForce RTX 4050, GDDR6 6GB/Urban Silver/2.1Kg), A13VE-031IN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    13,
                    15,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    16,
                    22,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    29,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    81,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    123,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    128,
                    132,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    134,
                    149,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS Vivobook S 15 OLED (2023), Intel Core EVO i5-13500H 13th Gen, 15.6\" (39.62 cm) 2.8K 120Hz OLED, Thin & Light Laptop (16GB/512GB SSD/Windows 11/Office 2021/75WHr/Silver/1.7 kg) S5504VA-MA543WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    18,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    25,
                    29,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    46,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    47,
                    65,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    71,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    74,
                    82,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    84,
                    87,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    120,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    122,
                    130,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    130,
                    132,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    133,
                    154,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "ASUS ROG Zephyrus Duo 16 Dual Screen Laptop, 16\" (40.64 cm) UHD+/FHD+ 120Hz/240Hz/3ms, AMD Ryzen 9 6900HX, 16GB RTX 3080 Ti, Gaming Laptop (32GB/2TB SSD/Win 11/Office/Black/2.55 Kg), GX650RXZ-LB226WS",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    5,
                    17,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    24,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    43,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    45,
                    47,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    58,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    85,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    87,
                    96,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    97,
                    105,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    107,
                    109,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    109,
                    111,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    116,
                    120,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    140,
                    146,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    183,
                    199,
                    "PERSON"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "LG Electronics 2023 Ultra 16-Inch Amd Ryzen7-7730U IPS Anti-Glare 16:10/16Gb Lpddr4X Ram/512Gb Ssd/Amd Radeon Graphic/Wqxga/1.47Kg/Face-Login/72Wh/3Yr Onsite-Warranty,Windows 11 Home",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    26,
                    44,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    151,
                    166,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HP 255 G8 Notebook PC,AMD Ryzen 3 3250U, 15.6 inch(39.6cm) Anti-Glare HD Laptop/8GB RAM/512GB SSD/Numeric Keypad/AMD Radeon Graphics/Win 11/1.74 Kgs 689T4PA",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    3,
                    6,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    31,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    32,
                    39,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    41,
                    57,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    81,
                    83,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    93,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    136,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo Yoga 6 AMD Ryzen 7 7730U 13.3\"(33.7cm) WUXGA 2-in-1 300Nits Laptop(16GB/1TB SSD/Win 11/Office 2021/Backlit KB/Digital Pen/1Yr Warranty/Alexa/3 month Game Pass/Dark Teal/1.37Kg), 83B2007UIN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    23,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    44,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    52,
                    53,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    101,
                    105,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    117,
                    141,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    156,
                    170,
                    "EVENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Microsoft Surface Laptop Go 3 (2024) - PixelSense Display, Intel Core i5-1245G7, 41WHrs Battery - (8 GB/256 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/45 W) THH-00024 Laptop (12.4 Inch, Ice Blue, 1.11 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    27,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    28,
                    29,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    59,
                    69,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    79,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    81,
                    87,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    152,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    154,
                    170,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    172,
                    181,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    193,
                    197,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Apple MacBook Air 13 (2024) - Apple M3, 52.6WHrs Battery - (8 GB/512 GB SSD/macOS/Integrated Graphics) Ultrabook (13.3 Inch, Gold, 1.25 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    22,
                    26,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    30,
                    35,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    48,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    69,
                    71,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    76,
                    102,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    114,
                    129,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    135,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "HCL ME Ultrabook U2 (2024) - AMD Ryzen 9 5900HX, 75WHrs Battery - (32 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/AMD Radeon Graphics) Ultrabook (14 Inch, Grey, 1.40 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    19,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    25,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    39,
                    47,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    49,
                    55,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    67,
                    69,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    75,
                    118,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    139,
                    143,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    145,
                    149,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "MSI Modern 15, Intel 13th Gen. i5-1335U, 40CM FHD 60Hz Laptop (16GB/512GB NVMe SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/Classic Black/1.7Kg), B13M-289IN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    13,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    20,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    34,
                    39,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    41,
                    49,
                    "MONEY"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    54,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    71,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    73,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    98,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    99,
                    123,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Samsung Galaxy Book3 360 (2024) - AMOLED Display, Intel EVO Platform, 54WHrs Battery, Intel Core i7-13700U - (16 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics/65 W) NP730QED-KA1US Convertible Laptop (13.3 Inch, Mystic Black, 1.16 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    14,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    24,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    26,
                    30,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    76,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    96,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    100,
                    106,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    112,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    118,
                    146,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    147,
                    168,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    170,
                    203,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    230,
                    237,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo IdeaPad Slim 5 (2024) - AMD Ryzen 5 5625U, 57WHrs Battery - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/AMD Radeon Graphics) Laptop (15.6 Inch, Abyss Blue, 1.85 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    40,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    41,
                    42,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    48,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    56,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    80,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    81,
                    128,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    130,
                    139,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    141,
                    151,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    153,
                    160,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "LG Ultra PC 16 (2024) - WQXGA IPS Display, AMD Ryzen 9 7940H, 72WHrs Battery - (32 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Radeon Graphics/65 W) 16U70Q-K.AAS8U1 Laptop (16 Inch, Black, 1.85 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    11,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    12,
                    14,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    43,
                    52,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    53,
                    60,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    62,
                    68,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    80,
                    82,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    88,
                    131,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    133,
                    139,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    157,
                    171,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    173,
                    180,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Infinix INBook X2 Plus (2024) - FHD IPS Display, Intel Core Platform, 50WHrs Battery, Intel Core i5-12500H - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Iris Xe Graphics/65 W) X2P-15 Laptop (15.6 Inch, Grey, 1.58 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    28,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    49,
                    54,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    70,
                    76,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    86,
                    96,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    119,
                    "MONEY"
                ],
                [
                    120,
                    122,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    142,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    143,
                    164,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    181,
                    190,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Lenovo Yoga Slim 7i Pro (2024) - 12th Gen Intel Core i5-1240P, 61WHrs Battery - (16 GB/512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics) 2-in-1 Laptop (14 Inch, Slate Grey, 1.39 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    16,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    17,
                    19,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    42,
                    47,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    69,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    91,
                    93,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    94,
                    119,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    125,
                    136,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    139,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    153,
                    160,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    162,
                    172,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    174,
                    178,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Samsung Galaxy Book3 Ultra (2024) - Dynamic AMOLED 2X Display, Intel EVO Platform, 76WHrs Battery, Intel Core i9-13900H - (32 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Home/RTX 4070/100 W) NP960XFH-X01US Laptop (16 Inch, Graphite, 1.79 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    21,
                    26,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    28,
                    32,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    89,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    123,
                    125,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    131,
                    168,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    170,
                    191,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    193,
                    200,
                    "TIME"
                ],
                [
                    212,
                    219,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Samsung Galaxy Book Odyssey (2024) - TFT Display, Intel Core i7-13700H, 83WHrs Battery - (32 GB/1 TB SSD/Windows 11 Pro/RTX 3050 Ti/95 W) NP760XDA-KA1US Gaming Laptop (15.6 Inch, Mystic Black, 1.85 Kg)",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    7,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    33,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    70,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    72,
                    78,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    90,
                    92,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    136,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    138,
                    166,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    168,
                    177,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    193,
                    200,
                    "PERCENT"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Acer Aspire 3 (Intel Core i3 1215U Processor/ 8GB/ 512 GB SSD/Windows 11 Home/MS Office) A315-59 with 39.6 cm (15.6\") Full HD Display /1.78kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    12,
                    13,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    20,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    34,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    51,
                    54,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    55,
                    57,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    58,
                    87,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    89,
                    96,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    102,
                    109,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    111,
                    115,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell Inspiron 7430 2in1 Touch Laptop, Intel Core i5-1335U Processor/ 16GB LP DDR5/ 1TB SSD/14.0\" (35.56cm) FHD+/ Active Pen/Win 11 + MSO'21/15 Month McAfee/Platinum Silver/Thin & Light- 1.58kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    36,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    38,
                    48,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    73,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    84,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    98,
                    105,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    149,
                    178,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Apple 2023 MacBook Pro (16-inch, M3 Max chip with 14â€‘core CPU and 30â€‘core GPU, 36GB Unified Memory, 1TB) - Space Black",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    22,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    24,
                    31,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    33,
                    39,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    60,
                    63,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    78,
                    81,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    83,
                    85,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    85,
                    87,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    104,
                    105,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "MSI Modern 14, Intel 12th Gen. i7-1255U, 36CM FHD 60Hz Laptop (16GB/512GB NVMe SSD/Windows 11 Home/Intel Iris Xe Graphics/Classic Black/1.4Kg), C12M-459IN",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    11,
                    13,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    15,
                    20,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    31,
                    39,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    50,
                    54,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    63,
                    71,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    71,
                    73,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    104,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    110,
                    129,
                    "ORG"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
    [
        "Dell G15-5530 Gaming Laptop, Intel Core i5-13450HX Processor, 16GB DDR5, 512GB,NVIDIA RTX 3050,6GB GDDR6, 15.6\" (39.62cm) FHD 120Hz 250 nits, Backlit KB Orange,Win 11 + MSO'21,Dark Shadow Gray, 2.65kg",
        {
            "entities": [
                [
                    0,
                    4,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    5,
                    13,
                    "DATE"
                ],
                [
                    14,
                    27,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    29,
                    39,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    40,
                    50,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    62,
                    64,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    64,
                    66,
                    "GPE"
                ],
                [
                    73,
                    78,
                    "PRODUCT"
                ],
                [
                    79,
                    85,
                    "ORG"
                ],
                [
                    90,
                    96,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    96,
                    104,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    106,
                    110,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    113,
                    121,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ],
                [
                    126,
                    135,
                    "CARDINAL"
                ],
                [
                    142,
                    159,
                    "PERSON"
                ],
                [
                    194,
                    200,
                    "QUANTITY"
                ]
            ]
        }
    ],
